友谊永存
Nothing stays the same for long
世界上没有什么是永恒不变的
But when it changes doesn't mean it's gone
但是变化并不意味着消失
Time will always get away
时光总是匆匆而逝
As it leaves behind another day
我们总是步履匆匆
Things may come and things may go
人生中许多事物来了又去
Some go fast and some go slow
有些会转瞬即逝 有些会慢慢消失踪影
Few things last that's all I know
很少有事物能够永恒不变
But friendship carries on through the ages
但是我们的友谊历经风风雨雨 仍然一如往日
Things may come and things may go
人生中许多事物来了又去
Some go fast and some go slow
有些会转瞬即逝 有些会慢慢消失踪影
Few things last that's all I know
很少有事物能够永恒不变
But friendship carries on through the ages
但是我们的友谊历经风风雨雨 仍然一如往日
Been around for a long time
长期以来 我被人群簇拥着
Rockin' out hard Cause I'm in my prime
拼尽全力 舞动出我的激情 因为我觉得我就是最棒的
Maybe it'll change further down the line
也许将来这一切都会完全改变
But my friendship carries on through the ages
但是我们的友谊历经风风雨雨 仍然一如往日
Every single style has somethin'
每一种个性都有独特的魅力
Different it can say
尽管可能会与众不同
There's nothin' wrong with bein' unique
但不走寻常路 并非错误之举
And special in your own way
你可以尽情施展自己独特的魅力
Maybe you wanna be a pop star
你也许想要成为流行之星
Get your fifteen minutes of fame
获得舞台上那转瞬即逝的荣誉
Wah-ah ah-oh
That won't last forever
那些都不会永存
But friendship remains the same
但是我们的友谊会永垂不朽
Ah oh
Things may come and things may go
人生中许多事物来了又去
Some go fast and some go slow
有些会转瞬即逝 有些会慢慢消失踪影
Few things last that's all I know
很少有事物能够永恒不变
But friendship carries on through the ages
但是我们的友谊历经风风雨雨 仍然一如往日
Things may come and things may go
人生中许多事物来了又去
Some go fast and some go slow
有些会转瞬即逝 有些会慢慢消失踪影
Few things last that's all I know
很少有事物能够永恒不变
But friendship carries on through the ages
但是我们的友谊历经风风雨雨 仍然一如往日
Ooh
Carries on
仍然一如往日